SON
ONE
GOD GAVE ME
OF
YEARS
HUNDRED
AFTER A
WAITING
TO CARRY
ME
THEN TOLD
MOUNTAIN
THE KNIFE UP A
HIM.
KILL
AND
ON
WOOD
I LAID THE
BACK
ISAAC'S
MY ONLY SON
LET
AND
HE WOULD
WOOD
CARRY THE
UPON.
DIE
LAMB
THE
HE ASKED WHERE
WAS.
WOULD
GOD
I TOLD HIM
ONE.
PROVIDE
HIM,
BOUND
I
KNIFE
RAISED THE
STOPPED MY
VOICE
AND A
HAND.
HUNG CAUGHT IN
RAM
A
THICKET,
IN MY
DIED
AND IT
PLACE.
SON'S
A RAM
GAVE
GOD
I SPOKE
LAMB
BUT THE
ON
FOUND
OF WAS NEVER
MOUNTAIN.
THAT
DELIVERED,
DOWN
I CAME
WAITING.
AND STILL
LATER,
GENERATIONS
JESUS
BELOVED SON
ANOTHER
OWN WOOD UP
HIS
CARRIED
SAME
A HILL IN THAT
LAND.
FATHER'S
STOPPED HIS
VOICE
NO
HAND
HIS OWN SON.
GAVE
HE
WAS CAUGHT FOR
RAM
NO
HIM,
LAMB.
HE WAS THE
BECAUSE
POINTED:
JOHN
A MAN NAMED
OF GOD,
LAMB
BEHOLD THE
THE SIN
AWAY
WHICH TAKETH
WORLD.
OF THE
ME:
ASKED
MY BOY
LAMB?
WHERE IS THE
TO
NAME
I HAD NO
HIM.
GIVE
DO.
YOU
HAS
GOD PROVIDED
LAMB
THE
NAME
A
JESUS,
YOU
MOUNTAIN
THE
WHO CLIMBED
COULD.
NEVER
DOWN,
KNIFE
LAY YOUR
HIM.
RECEIVE
AND